Read a story
读故事
The wrong way
错误的道路
Dot and Dan ring May and Jack on the telephone.
点点和丹在给麦和杰克打电话
“Hi, May! When can you go out? At ten a.m.?
你好 麦 你什么时候出来 十点吗
Good."
好
Jack says.
杰克说
“Knock at our door.
敲我们家的门
It is a blue house on Green Street.
在格林大街上有一栋蓝色的房子
You know the way."
你知道怎么来
Dot says to Dan.
点点对丹说
“You can go to the blue house with me."
你可以和我一起去蓝色房子
“OK. Thanks."
好的  谢谢
says Dan.
丹说
“This is the right way,"
这是对的路
says Dan.
丹说
“No, that is the wrong way."
不 那是错误的路
says Dot.
点点说
“This is the right way."
这是正确的路
says Dot.
点点说
“No, that is the wrong way."
不  那是错误的路
says Dan.
丹说
“This is Green Street,"
这是格林大街
says Dot.
点点说
“No, this is Yellow Street,"
不 这是耶鲁大街
says Dan.
丹说
“but it has green houses."
但是它有绿色的房子
“This is the wrong street."
这是错误的街道
“This is Green Street!"
这是格林大街
says Dot.
点点说
“Look, I can see a blue house!"
看 我看见了一个蓝色的房子
Dan says.
丹说
“Quick! Run with me!"
快 和我一起跑
Knock, knock, knock!
咚 咚 咚
“Hi, Dan! Hi, Dot!"
丹 点点 你们好
says Jack.
杰克说
“Now we can go out to play!"
现在我们可以出去玩了
“No, thank you!"
不 谢谢你
says Dot.
点点说
“No, thank you!"
不 谢谢你
says Dan.
丹说
“We need to sit down!"
我们要坐下来